<resources>
    <string name="app_name">True or False?</string>
    <string name="fileForQuestions">filequestions</string>
    <string name="buttonFalseText">Ложь</string>
    <string name="buttonTrueText">Правда</string>
    <string name="CountCurrentUserAnswers" translatable="false">0</string>
    <string name="CountUserNotCurrentAnswers" translatable="false">0</string>
    <string name="hintOfCurrentAnswer">..коснитесь экрана для возврата..</string>
    <string name="buttonStart_Text">Начать</string>
    <string name="buttonSetting_Text">Настройки</string>
    <string name="buttonExit_Text">Выход</string>
    <string name="textViewQuestionsBar">Общее количество вопросов:</string>
    <string name="textViewAnswerBar">Правильные ответы:</string>
    <string name="textView_Result_CurrentAnswers_Text">Количество правильных ответов:</string>
    <string name="textView_Result_NotCurrentAnswers_Text">Количество неправильных ответов:</string>
    <string name="textView_RatioAnswers_Text">Коэффициент правильных ответов:</string>
    <string name="textView_Result_CountOfQuestionsResult">100</string>
    <string name="textView_Result_CurrentAnswers_Result">30</string>
    <string name="textView_Result_NotCurrentAnswers_Result">70</string>
    <string name="textView_RatioAnswers_Result">30%</string>
    <string name="buttonResume_Text">Продолжить</string>
    <string name="CountCurrentUserAntiLives" translatable="false">0</string>
    <string name="CountCurrentUserLives" translatable="false">5</string>
    <string name="textViewLivesBar">Количество возможных ошибок:</string>
    <string name="RateForApp">Если вам понравилось это приложение, то проголосуйте за него или напишите комментарий:</string>
    <string name="textView_Result1_HeadText">Плохо</string>
    <string name="textView_Result1_BodyText">Вы показали очень плохой результат. Повышайте свою эрудицию.</string>
    <string name="textView_Result2_BodyText">  У вас посредственный результат. Необходимо всесторонне развиваться.</string>
    <string name="textView_Result2_HeadText">Удовлетворительно</string>
    <string name="textView_Result3_BodyText">Показатель хорошей образованности. Но не стоит расслабляться.</string>
    <string name="textView_Result3_HeadText">Хорошо</string>
    <string name="textView_Result4_BodyText">Ваши знания помогают вам в жизни. Не многие достигли такого результата.</string>
    <string name="textView_Result4_HeadText">Замечательно</string>
    <string name="textView_Result5_BodyText">Полученный результат отражает большой труд в накоплении знаний.</string>
    <string name="textView_Result5_HeadText">Великолепно</string>
    <string name="_q001">The caterpillar muscle more than the man.</string>
    <string name="_q002">Non-stop flight of a dove may exceed 40 000 kilometres.</string>
    <string name="_q003">Rabbits run faster than hare.</string>
    <string name="_q004">Purebred pigeon was bought for $200,000.</string>
    <string name="_q005">In Australia, over-population of rabbits — a national disaster.</string>
    <string name="_q006">Unripe tomatoes are poisonous.</string>
    <string name="_q007">Pink flamingos have this color since birth.</string>
    <string name="_q008">Camels tolerate dehydration due to the particular structure of red blood cells.</string>
    <string name="_q009">The temperature of the blood of certain fishes may be below zero degrees Celsius.</string>
    <string name="_q010">The fastest mammal on Earth - hare.</string>
    <string name="_q011">Cow per day produce more saliva than milk.</string>
    <string name="_q012">Lemon can not weigh more than 1 kilogram.</string>
    <string name="_q013">A cow can distinguish bitter milk.</string>
    <string name="_q014">Mosquitoes, when choosing who to attack, guided only by the body temperature.</string>
    <string name="_q015">Cows on the Earth more than people.</string>
    <string name="_q016">In the Russian cartoon Mowgli Bagheera is female.</string>
    <string name="_q017">The first Bicycle lane appeared in Russia over 100 years ago.</string>
    <string name="_q018">Strings for violins were originally made of animals.</string>
    <string name="_q019">Dolphins call each other by individual names.</string>
    <string name="_q020">The oldest rose Bush about 1000 years.</string>
    <string name="_q021">The early carrots were purple.</string>
    <string name="_q022">There are fish that can live on land.</string>
    <string name="_q023">Penguins can only live in cold climates.</string>
    <string name="_q024">In Thailand, all cats are Siamese.</string>
    <string name="_q025">Koalas almost do not drink the water.</string>
    <string name="_q026">In Russian and English languages is the word for the opposite direction of the knee.</string>
    <string name="_q027">The flint inside the lighter\'s not real.</string>
    <string name="_q028">There is a country where postage is free.</string>
    <string name="_q029">Males mosquitoes do not feed on blood.</string>
    <string name="_q030">The most expensive caviar is sturgeon black.</string>
    <string name="_q031">The shortest television commercial lasts 5 seconds.</string>
    <string name="_q032">Russian TV program \"Club of film travel\" hit the Guinness book of records.</string>
    <string name="_q033">The most popular girl\'s name - Catherine.</string>
    <string name="_q034">The character of the novel \"Heart of a Dog\" Professor Preobrazhensky is a living prototype.</string>
    <string name="_q035">The longest musical piece lasts for over 500 years.</string>
    <string name="_q036">Polar bears have white skin.</string>
    <string name="_q037">Some of the aborigines of Australia the language of communication there is a fourth gender.</string>
    <string name="_q038">Papa Carlo in the Russian film \"Pinocchio\" is a real person.</string>
    <string name="_q039">In order to recognize the subject of fine art enough opinion of one person.</string>
    <string name="_q040">Russian language is a list of the official languages of the UN.</string>
    <string name="_q041">There is a rose that changes color of its petals during the day.</string>
    <string name="_q042">In Belgium there are outdoor toilets for dogs.</string>
    <string name="_q043">Starfish have a number of eyes corresponding to the number of limbs.</string>
    <string name="_q044">Lightning strikes upwards.</string>
    <string name="_q045">Chinese typewriters more than 5,000 keys.</string>
    <string name="_q046">Sundress clothes were for men.</string>
    <string name="_q047">Skirt is in uniform only Scottish army.</string>
    <string name="_q048">In a few hundred years cease to be born blond.</string>
    <string name="_q049">Hamlet was not written by William Shakespeare.</string>
    <string name="_q050">10% Land living animals still exist.</string>
    <string name="_q051">In Russia, the coins were less than one penny.</string>
    <string name="_q052">There are duels on the peacock feathers.</string>
    <string name="_q053">Music may have a \"Platinum record\", but do not have a \"Gold record\".</string>
    <string name="_q054">The sun is not yellow.</string>
    <string name="_q055">Tape worms can eat themselves.</string>
    <string name="_q056">Hair is the hardest tissue in the human.</string>
    <string name="_q057">The word \"Hermitage\" means \"beautiful room\".</string>
    <string name="_q058">Weight of ink to one point in the text of the newspaper not less than 0.1 gram.</string>
    <string name="_q059">Pluto revolves around the Sun at more than 200 times slower than the Earth.</string>
    <string name="_q060">Coffee is the most purchased goods on the international market.</string>
    <string name="_q061">Musical instrument \"faggot\" only do one tree.</string>
    <string name="_q062">The number of teeth in the born identical twins the same.</string>
    <string name="_q063">Australia is not moving around the world.</string>
    <string name="_q064">The largest amount of vitamin C is in oranges.</string>
    <string name="_q065">The mole can\'t dig a hole and hide in it for 1 minute.</string>
    <string name="_q066">Neanderthal brain less brain of modern man.</string>
    <string name="_q067">Rhyme about Humpty Dumpty was dedicated to a specific person.</string>
    <string name="_q068">In place of fallen hair nothing else grows.</string>
    <string name="_q069">Heated iron never evaporates.</string>
    <string name="_q070">Half of the earth\'s Land surface is desert.</string>
    <string name="_q071">There is a TV channel that only shows fish.</string>
    <string name="_q072">The internal surface area of human lungs is equal to the area of the unfolded newspaper.</string>
    <string name="_q073">Jean Claude van Damme does not have an alias, ie, that\'s his real name.</string>
    <string name="_q074">Every year on Earth is not more than 10,000 earthquakes.</string>
    <string name="_q075">Snakes do not distinguish between the sounds.</string>
    <string name="_q076">In Russian dictionaries there is no word \"buzzing\".</string>
    <string name="_q077">No one found the diamond was more than 3,000 carats.</string>
    <string name="_q078">Absolutely pure gold is very solid.</string>
    <string name="_q079">Grapes cannot be heated in a microwave oven.</string>
    <string name="_q080">Drownings can live.</string>
    <string name="_q081">Everyone who went down Niagara falls in a barrel survived.</string>
    <string name="_q082">Between the birth of twins can\'t go more than 1 day.</string>
    <string name="_q083">Arabic numerals invented by the Arabs.</string>
    <string name="_q084">Every year all people of the planet consumed more than half a trillion chicken eggs.</string>
    <string name="_q085">Roquefort cheese is made from horse\'s milk.</string>
    <string name="_q086">On the walk of fame is dedicated to the cartoon character.</string>
    <string name="_q087">The most ancient plant on the Ground - clover.</string>
    <string name="_q088">The main part of the composition of household dust cloth.</string>
    <string name="_q089">20% of bacteria known to mankind, threat to human health.</string>
    <string name="_q090">Eskimos have no word for snow.</string>
    <string name="_q091">On the International space station has the bell.</string>
    <string name="_q092">Chinese more than rabbits in Australia.</string>
    <string name="_q093">Cinderella lost her right shoe.</string>
    <string name="_q094">The most long-lived mammal on Earth - an elephant.</string>
    <string name="_q095">The number of stars in our galaxy consistently.</string>
    <string name="_q096">In the language of the citizens of Papua have only two words denoting color.</string>
    <string name="_q097">From snake bites kills more people than bee stings.</string>
    <string name="_q098">Russian word \"doctor\" comes from the word \"lie\".</string>
    <string name="_q099">In Britain banned some stick brand, turning them.</string>
    <string name="_q100">Proton heavier than an electron.</string>
    <string name="_q101">Buddha lived 2000 years.</string>
    <string name="_q102">There is a body of water \"dead,\" Dead Sea.</string>
    <string name="_q103">In one of the cities in the US it is prohibited in the street with no money.</string>
    <string name="_q104">The head of an elephant brain weighs 5% of its weight.</string>
    <string name="_q105">In the past, the British necessarily carry a whistle.</string>
    <string name="_q106">Children in Finland do not believe in the existence of Santa Claus.</string>
    <string name="_q107">Some cars have under the feet of the driver\'s hatch for fishing.</string>
    <string name="_q108">Diamond and diamond are the same in composition.</string>
    <string name="_q109">You can see a rainbow and the sun at the same time.</string>
    <string name="_q110">All the gold of the Earth placed in the Olympic pool.</string>
    <string name="_q111">In the maritime terminology meaning of the word \"vessel\" and \"ship\" is the same.</string>
    <string name="_q112">In February, it is only 28 or 29 days.</string>
    <string name="_q113">In February, it is only 28 or 29 days.</string>
    <string name="_q114">The biggest screw-nut weighs over 4 tons.</string>
    <string name="_q115">On one of the flags of the countries of the world shows the constellation of another solar system.</string>
    <string name="_q116">The logo of the company Nestle has always been depicted three birds.</string>
    <string name="_q117">Not all of the astronauts of Apollo 11 crew were on the lunar surface.</string>
    <string name="_q118">Puzzle Rubik\'s Cube can be collected for at least 15 moves.</string>
    <string name="_q119">Thai alphabet - the largest in the world.</string>
    <string name="_q120">Denominations of $2 does not exist.</string>
    <string name="_q121">Darwin crater on the Moon is named in honor of Charles Darwin (theory of evolution).</string>
    <string name="_q122">Mount Everest has always been the highest point of the Earth.</string>
    <string name="_q123">The biggest teddy bear weighs less than 1 tonne.</string>
    <string name="_q124">The phrase \"money does not smell,\" invented by the Romans.</string>
    <string name="_q125">The diameter of the circus arena in different circuses different from each other.</string>
    <string name="_q126">Recipe for bread was found due to an error.</string>
    <string name="_q127">The largest number of trams in Moscow.</string>
    <string name="_q128">For some people, milk is poison.</string>
    <string name="_q129">There are celestial bodies, called \"The Beatles\" in honor of the group of singers.</string>
    <string name="_q130">\"Fanta\" - the second most popular soft drink in the world.</string>
    <string name="_q131">\"Big Ben\" - the most famous English clock.</string>
    <string name="_q132">Milk tooth can not fall out.</string>
    <string name="_q133">The biggest snowman ice cream was made in Russia.</string>
    <string name="_q134">In the Moscow subway escalators have only stations, which are at a depth of 10 meters.</string>
    <string name="_q135">Raw egg can fall from a height of about 200 meters and did not break.</string>
    <string name="_q136">The largest pearl weighing more than 6 kg.</string>
    <string name="_q137">In humans, all the fingers straight.</string>
    <string name="_q138">The sound of \"A\" has all the languages of the peoples of the Earth.</string>
    <string name="_q139">Defunct literary character Sherlock Holmes sends real postal letters.</string>
    <string name="_q140">The most common disease - influenza.</string>
    <string name="_q141">The chewing gum is not added dyes.</string>
    <string name="_q142">Sandals - the oldest shoes.</string>
    <string name="_q143">Baby diapers decompose within 10 years.</string>
    <string name="_q144">Woodpeckers - a real threat to the development of space programs throughout the world.</string>
    <string name="_q145">In Russian felt boots is no difference between \"left\" and \"right\".</string>
    <string name="_q146">In weightlessness height increases.</string>
    <string name="_q147">Queen Victoria gave the wedding a piece of cheese.</string>
    <string name="_q148">The bulk of the extracted titanium is used to create durable alloys.</string>
    <string name="_q149">\"Balzac Age\" - from 40 years and above.</string>
    <string name="_q150">\"The game is not worth the candle,\" now means that the cost of some business higher potential income from it.</string>
    <string name="_q151">The greatest amount of hair growing on the head.</string>
    <string name="_q152">The alloy from which created the Tsar Bell contain gold and silver.</string>
    <string name="_q153">All pages created in VKontakte Today, you can see 100 years.</string>
    <string name="_q154">All pages created in VKontakte Today, you can see 100 years.</string>
    <string name="_q155">VKontakte - the most visited site in RuNet.</string>
    <string name="_q156">By accessing the site foogle.com, get on the google.com site.</string>
    <string name="_q157">Detonating cord is burning evenly.</string>
    <string name="_q158">The shortest line thinner than a human hair.</string>
    <string name="_q159">All the organs of the human body refreshed.</string>
    <string name="_q160">Earth day is 24 hours.</string>
    <string name="_q161">Earth\'s day length remains unchanged.</string>
    <string name="_q162">The highest temperature on Earth is equal to 45,5 °C.</string>
    <string name="_q163">The lowest temperature on Earth is equal to -89,1 °C.</string>
    <string name="_q164">Mercury (the planet closest to the Sun) - the hottest planet in the solar system.</string>
    <string name="_q165">Water freezes at 0 °C.</string>
    <string name="_q166">The Martian day equal to the terrestrial day.</string>
    <string name="_q167">Platinum was cheaper silver.</string>
    <string name="_q168">The magnetic field of a neutron star is a million million times larger than the Earth\'s magnetic field.</string>
    <string name="_q169">Most of iodine contained in seaweed.</string>
    <string name="_q170">Ozone protects us from solar radiation, toxic.</string>
    <string name="_q171">Some metals are not drown in the liquid.</string>
    <string name="_q172">From the consumption of ordinary table salt to die for.</string>
    <string name="_q173">Soap bubble bursts faster than the duration of a nuclear reaction.</string>
    <string name="_q174">Underground water is more than in all the oceans.</string>
    <string name="_q175">Man does not see the infrared or ultraviolet radiation.</string>
    <string name="_q176">The atomic clock always shows the correct time.</string>
    <string name="_q177">The temperature of the resulting person below the temperature of the sun.</string>
    <string name="_q178">The Martian atmosphere contains carbon dioxide.</string>
    <string name="_q179">Giraffes to brush his eyes blinking rapidly.</string>
    <string name="_q180">Mona Lisa displayed without eyebrows.</string>
    <string name="_q181">Eminem - the most sold-out hip-hop artist in the world.</string>
    <string name="_q182">Lunatics better not to wake, as this could ruin their psyche because of the abrupt awakening.</string>
    <string name="_q183">If you jump into the icy water, you can catch a cold.</string>
    <string name="_q184">After death of his nails and hair continue to grow for some time.</string>
    <string name="_q185">If you shave, then re-growing hair will be thicker and darker.</string>
    <string name="_q186">A man uses only 10% of his brain.</string>
    <string name="_q187">Warts may occur after contact with animals.</string>
    <string name="_q188">Before Coco Chanel\'s death has created a fund to which to this day are deductions from sales of famous perfume \"Chanel №5».</string>
    <string name="_q189">Einstein almost 9 years could not speak properly.</string>
    <string name="_q190">Russian tsar Peter I often worked as a discharge dentistry - tore bad teeth.</string>
    <string name="_q191">Albert Einstein received the Nobel Prize for the creation of the theory of relativity.</string>
    <string name="_q192">During the struggle for independence, when George Washington was still commander of the rebel army, he tried to poison tomatoes.</string>
    <string name="_q193">Eye color can change throughout life.</string>
    <string name="_q194">Если бросить в воду свежее куриное яйцо, оно утонет.</string>
    <string name="_q195">The taste that you feel today is a bit different from the taste that you felt a week ago.</string>
    <string name="_q196">The most common words in the world: \"I love you\".</string>
    <string name="_q197">Every day, the Earth becomes 10 tons heavier.</string>
    <string name="_q198">Dolphins sleep with one eye open.</string>
    <string name="_q199">Aladdin was Iranian.</string>
    <string name="_q200">Do bats rectangular pupils.</string>
    <string name="_q201">Orca - a kind of shark.</string>
    <string name="_q202">\"Mother\" - the most popular word in the world.</string>
    <string name="_q203">Gorged itself chocolate to die for.</string>
    <string name="_q204">The most deadly creature - a shark.</string>
    <string name="_q205">Adult skeleton consists of 300 bones.</string>
    <string name="_q206">Hedgehog is back on the apple to eat it later.</string>
    <string name="_q207">Storks can sleep during the flight.</string>
    <string name="_q208">The cat was the king of Norway.</string>
    <string name="_q209">Teddy Bear was named in honor of Theodore Roosevelt.</string>
    <string name="_q210">Rats laugh from schekotok.</string>
    <string name="_q211">Married men over unmarried.</string>
    <string name="_q212">Penterafobiya - fear of Tiffany.</string>
    <string name="_q213">Giraffe\'s neck has 21 vertebrae.</string>
    <string name="_q214">In one country, people live in the cemetery.</string>
    <string name="_q215">The sum of all the numbers on the roulette wheel is equal to the number 666.</string>
    <string name="_q216">In Norway, always give way to the elderly.</string>
    <string name="_q217">Owls can not move their eyes.</string>
    <string name="_q218">Chewing gum is digested in the stomach for seven years.</string>
    <string name="_q219">Rabbits can only look forward.</string>
    <string name="_q220">Paparazzi - Italian photographer.</string>
    <string name="_q221">The strongest muscle in the human - leg muscle.</string>
    <string name="_q222">Do hippos pink milk.</string>
    <string name="_q223">The shelf life of honey - 10 years.</string>
    <string name="_q224">At the octopus has no heart.</string>
    <string name="_q225">Peanuts - a nut.</string>
    <string name="_q226">Fanta came up with the Germans.</string>
    <string name="_q227">Lake Michigan - the largest lake in the world.</string>
    <string name="_q228">The cow - the only mammal that can not jump.</string>
    <string name="_q229">Ostrich egg is cooked poultry quickly.</string>
    <string name="_q230">In India, no monkeys.</string>
    <string name="_q231">The German Shepherd Dog blue tongue.</string>
    <string name="_q232">Paper money is made from paper.</string>
    <string name="_q233">A sheet of paper can not be folded in half more than 5 times.</string>
    <string name="_q234">Bulimia - the refusal of eating food.</string>
    <string name="_q235">Whale Heart makes a 9 beats per minute.</string>
    <string name="_q236">The fastest flying insect - a wasp.</string>
    <string name="_q237">Elephant bears posterity 12 months.</string>
    <string name="_q238">Elephant - the largest animal.</string>
    <string name="_q239">Ant - the strongest insect.</string>
    <string name="_q240">The most intelligent bird - a parrot.</string>
    <string name="_q241">In some animals blood blue.</string>
    <string name="_q242">Do snails have no teeth.</string>
    <string name="_q243">Ostriches bury their heads in the sand.</string>
    <string name="_q244">Do mosquitoes have teeth.</string>
    <string name="_q245">Heart stops, even in healthy people.</string>
    <string name="_q246">In the mobile phone a lot of gold.</string>
    <string name="_q247">Crocodile Gena Soviet cartoon - not a crocodile.</string>
    <string name="_q248">Dragonfly lives 4 months.</string>
    <string name="_q249">Sharks never get sick.</string>
    <string name="_q250">All the planets in our solar system orbit in the same direction.</string>
</resources>
