<resources>
    <string name="app_name">True or False?</string>
    <string name="fileForQuestions">filequestions</string>
    <string name="buttonFalseText">Ложь</string>
    <string name="buttonTrueText">Правда</string>
    <string name="CountCurrentUserAnswers" translatable="false">0</string>
    <string name="CountUserNotCurrentAnswers" translatable="false">0</string>
    <string name="hintOfCurrentAnswer">..коснитесь экрана для возврата..</string>
    <string name="buttonStart_Text">Начать</string>
    <string name="buttonSetting_Text">Настройки</string>
    <string name="buttonExit_Text">Выход</string>
    <string name="textViewQuestionsBar">Общее количество вопросов:</string>
    <string name="textViewAnswerBar">Правильные ответы:</string>
    <string name="textView_Result_CurrentAnswers_Text">Количество правильных ответов:</string>
    <string name="textView_Result_NotCurrentAnswers_Text">Количество неправильных ответов:</string>
    <string name="textView_RatioAnswers_Text">Коэффициент правильных ответов:</string>
    <string name="textView_Result_CountOfQuestionsResult" translatable="false">100</string>
    <string name="textView_Result_CurrentAnswers_Result" translatable="false">30</string>
    <string name="textView_Result_NotCurrentAnswers_Result" translatable="false">70</string>
    <string name="textView_RatioAnswers_Result" translatable="false">30%</string>
    <string name="buttonResume_Text">Продолжить</string>
    <string name="CountCurrentUserAntiLives" translatable="false">0</string>
    <string name="CountCurrentUserLives" translatable="false">5</string>
    <string name="textViewLivesBar">Количество возможных ошибок:</string>
    <string name="RateForApp">Если вам понравилось это приложение, то проголосуйте за него или напишите комментарий:</string>
    <string name="textView_Result1_HeadText">Плохо</string>
    <string name="textView_Result1_BodyText">Вы показали очень плохой результат. Повышайте свою эрудицию.</string>
    <string name="textView_Result2_BodyText">  У вас посредственный результат. Необходимо всесторонне развиваться.</string>
    <string name="textView_Result2_HeadText">Удовлетворительно</string>
    <string name="textView_Result3_BodyText">Показатель хорошей образованности. Но не стоит расслабляться.</string>
    <string name="textView_Result3_HeadText">Хорошо</string>
    <string name="textView_Result4_BodyText">Ваши знания помогают вам в жизни. Не многие достигли такого результата.</string>
    <string name="textView_Result4_HeadText">Замечательно</string>
    <string name="textView_Result5_BodyText">Полученный результат отражает большой труд в накоплении знаний.</string>
    <string name="textView_Result5_HeadText">Великолепно</string>
    <string name="_q001">The caterpillar muscle more than the man.</string>
    <string name="_q002">Non-stop flight of a dove may exceed 40 000 kilometres.</string>
    <string name="_q003">Rabbits run faster than hare.</string>
    <string name="_q004">Purebred pigeon was bought for $200,000.</string>
    <string name="_q005">In Australia, over-population of rabbits — a national disaster.</string>
    <string name="_q006">Unripe tomatoes are poisonous.</string>
    <string name="_q007">Pink flamingos have this color since birth.</string>
    <string name="_q008">Camels tolerate dehydration due to the particular structure of red blood cells.</string>
    <string name="_q009">The temperature of the blood of certain fishes may be below zero degrees Celsius.</string>
    <string name="_q010">The fastest mammal on Earth - hare.</string>
    <string name="_q011">Cow per day produce more saliva than milk.</string>
    <string name="_q012">Lemon can not weigh more than 1 kilogram.</string>
    <string name="_q013">A cow can distinguish bitter milk.</string>
    <string name="_q014">Mosquitoes, when choosing who to attack, guided only by the body temperature.</string>
    <string name="_q015">Cows on the Earth more than people.</string>
    <string name="_q016">In the Russian cartoon Mowgli Bagheera is female.</string>
    <string name="_q017">The first Bicycle lane appeared in Russia over 100 years ago.</string>
    <string name="_q018">Strings for violins were originally made of animals.</string>
    <string name="_q019">Dolphins call each other by individual names.</string>
    <string name="_q020">The oldest rose Bush about 1000 years.</string>
    <string name="_q021">The early carrots were purple.</string>
    <string name="_q022">There are fish that can live on land.</string>
    <string name="_q023">Penguins can only live in cold climates.</string>
    <string name="_q024">In Thailand, all cats are Siamese.</string>
    <string name="_q025">Koalas almost do not drink the water.</string>
    <string name="_q026">In Russian and English languages is the word for the opposite direction of the knee.</string>
    <string name="_q027">The flint inside the lighter\'s not real.</string>
    <string name="_q028">There is a country where postage is free.</string>
    <string name="_q029">Males mosquitoes do not feed on blood.</string>
    <string name="_q030">The most expensive caviar is sturgeon black.</string>
    <string name="_q031">The shortest television commercial lasts 5 seconds.</string>
    <string name="_q032">Russian TV program \"Travel club\" hit the Guinness book of records.</string>
    <string name="_q033">The most popular girl\'s name - Catherine.</string>
    <string name="_q034">The character of the novel \"Heart of a Dog\" Professor Preobrazhensky is a living prototype.</string>
    <string name="_q035">The longest musical piece lasts for over 500 years.</string>
    <string name="_q036">Polar bears have white skin.</string>
    <string name="_q037">Some of the aborigines of Australia the language of communication there is a fourth gender.</string>
    <string name="_q038">Papa Carlo in the Russian film \"Pinocchio\" is a real person.</string>
    <string name="_q039">In order to recognize the subject of fine art enough opinion of one person.</string>
    <string name="_q040">Russian language is a list of the official languages of the UN.</string>
    <string name="_q041">There is a rose that changes color of its petals during the day.</string>
    <string name="_q042">In Belgium there are outdoor toilets for dogs.</string>
    <string name="_q043">Starfish have a number of eyes corresponding to the number of limbs.</string>
    <string name="_q044">Lightning strikes upwards.</string>
    <string name="_q045">Chinese typewriters more than 5,000 keys.</string>
    <string name="_q046">Sundress clothes were for men.</string>
    <string name="_q047">Skirt is in uniform only Scottish army.</string>
    <string name="_q048">In a few hundred years cease to be born blond.</string>
    <string name="_q049">Hamlet was not written by William Shakespeare.</string>
    <string name="_q050">10% Land living animals still exist.</string>
    <string name="_q051">In Russia, the coins were less than one penny.</string>
    <string name="_q052">There are duels on the peacock feathers.</string>
    <string name="_q053">The musical composition may have a \"Platinum Disc\", but did not have a \"Golden Disc\".</string>
    <string name="_q054">The sun is not yellow.</string>
    <string name="_q055">Tape worms can eat themselves.</string>
    <string name="_q056">Hair is the hardest tissue in the human.</string>
    <string name="_q057">The word \"Hermitage\" means \"beautiful room\".</string>
    <string name="_q058">Weight of ink to one point in the text of the newspaper not less than 0.1 gram.</string>
    <string name="_q059">Pluto revolves around the Sun at more than 200 times slower than the Earth.</string>
    <string name="_q060">Coffee is the most purchased goods on the international market.</string>
    <string name="_q061">Musical instrument \"faggot\" only do one tree.</string>
    <string name="_q062">The number of teeth in the born identical twins the same.</string>
    <string name="_q063">Australia is not moving around the world.</string>
    <string name="_q064">The largest amount of vitamin C is in oranges.</string>
    <string name="_q065">The mole can\'t dig a hole and hide in it for 1 minute.</string>
    <string name="_q066">Neanderthal brain less brain of modern man.</string>
    <string name="_q067">Rhyme about Humpty Dumpty was dedicated to a specific person.</string>
    <string name="_q068">In place of fallen hair nothing else grows.</string>
    <string name="_q069">Heated iron never evaporates.</string>
    <string name="_q070">Half of the earth\'s Land surface is desert.</string>
    <string name="_q071">There is a TV channel that only shows fish.</string>
    <string name="_q072">The internal surface area of human lungs is equal to the area of the unfolded newspaper.</string>
    <string name="_q073">Jean Claude van Damme does not have an alias, ie, that\'s his real name.</string>
    <string name="_q074">Every year on Earth is not more than 10,000 earthquakes.</string>
    <string name="_q075">Snakes do not distinguish between the sounds.</string>
    <string name="_q076">In Russian dictionaries there is no word \"buzzing\".</string>
    <string name="_q077">No one found the diamond was more than 3,000 carats.</string>
    <string name="_q078">Absolutely pure gold is very solid.</string>
    <string name="_q079">Grapes cannot be heated in a microwave oven.</string>
    <string name="_q080">Drownings can live.</string>
    <string name="_q081">Everyone who went down Niagara falls in a barrel survived.</string>
    <string name="_q082">Between the birth of twins can\'t go more than 1 day.</string>
    <string name="_q083">Arabic numerals invented by the Arabs.</string>
    <string name="_q084">Every year all people of the planet consumed more than half a trillion chicken eggs.</string>
    <string name="_q085">Roquefort cheese is made from horse\'s milk.</string>
    <string name="_q086">On the walk of fame is dedicated to the cartoon character.</string>
    <string name="_q087">The most ancient plant on the Ground - clover.</string>
    <string name="_q088">The main part of the composition of household dust cloth.</string>
    <string name="_q089">20% of bacteria known to mankind, threat to human health.</string>
    <string name="_q090">Eskimos have no word for snow.</string>
    <string name="_q091">On the International space station has the bell.</string>
    <string name="_q092">Chinese more than rabbits in Australia.</string>
    <string name="_q093">Cinderella lost her right shoe.</string>
    <string name="_q094">The most long-lived mammal on Earth - an elephant.</string>
    <string name="_q095">The number of stars in our galaxy consistently.</string>
    <string name="_q096">In the language of the citizens of Papua have only two words denoting color.</string>
    <string name="_q097">From snake bites kills more people than bee stings.</string>
    <string name="_q098">Russian word \"doctor\" comes from the word \"lie\".</string>
    <string name="_q099">In Britain banned some stick brand, turning them.</string>
    <string name="_q100">Proton heavier than an electron.</string>
    <string name="_q101">Buddha lived 2000 years.</string>
    <string name="_q102">There is a body of water \"dead,\" Dead Sea.</string>
    <string name="_q103">In one of the cities in the US it is prohibited in the street with no money.</string>
    <string name="_q104">The head of an elephant brain weighs 5% of its weight.</string>
    <string name="_q105">In the past, the British necessarily carry a whistle.</string>
    <string name="_q106">Children in Finland do not believe in the existence of Santa Claus.</string>
    <string name="_q107">Some cars have under the feet of the driver\'s hatch for fishing.</string>
    <string name="_q108">Diamond and diamond are the same in composition.</string>
    <string name="_q109">You can see a rainbow and the sun at the same time.</string>
    <string name="_q110">All the gold of the Earth placed in the Olympic pool.</string>
    <string name="_q111">In the maritime terminology meaning of the word \"vessel\" and \"ship\" is the same.</string>
    <string name="_q112">In February, it is only 28 or 29 days.</string>
    <string name="_q113">In February, it is only 28 or 29 days.</string>
    <string name="_q114">The biggest screw-nut weighs over 4 tons.</string>
    <string name="_q115">On one of the flags of the countries of the world shows the constellation of another solar system.</string>
    <string name="_q116">The logo of the company Nestle has always been depicted three birds.</string>
    <string name="_q117">Not all of the astronauts of Apollo 11 crew were on the lunar surface.</string>
    <string name="_q118">Puzzle Rubik\'s Cube can be collected for at least 15 moves.</string>
    <string name="_q119">Thai alphabet - the largest in the world.</string>
    <string name="_q120">Denominations of $2 does not exist.</string>
    <string name="_q121">Darwin crater on the Moon is named in honor of Charles Darwin (theory of evolution).</string>
    <string name="_q122">Mount Everest has always been the highest point of the Earth.</string>
    <string name="_q123">The biggest teddy bear weighs less than 1 tonne.</string>
    <string name="_q124">The phrase \"money does not smell,\" invented by the Romans.</string>
    <string name="_q125">The diameter of the circus arena in different circuses different from each other.</string>
    <string name="_q126">Recipe for bread was found due to an error.</string>
    <string name="_q127">The largest number of trams in Moscow.</string>
    <string name="_q128">For some people, milk is poison.</string>
    <string name="_q129">There are celestial bodies, called \"The Beatles\" in honor of the group of singers.</string>
    <string name="_q130">\"Fanta\" - the second most popular soft drink in the world.</string>
    <string name="_q131">\"Big Ben\" - the most famous English clock.</string>
    <string name="_q132">Milk tooth can not fall out.</string>
    <string name="_q133">The biggest snowman ice cream was made in Russia.</string>
    <string name="_q134">In the Moscow subway escalators have only stations, which are at a depth of 10 meters.</string>
    <string name="_q135">Raw egg can fall from a height of about 200 meters and did not break.</string>
    <string name="_q136">The largest pearl weighing more than 6 kg.</string>
    <string name="_q137">In humans, all the fingers straight.</string>
    <string name="_q138">The sound of \"A\" has all the languages of the peoples of the Earth.</string>
    <string name="_q139">Defunct literary character Sherlock Holmes sends real postal letters.</string>
    <string name="_q140">The most common disease - influenza.</string>
    <string name="_q141">The chewing gum is not added dyes.</string>
    <string name="_q142">Sandals - the oldest shoes.</string>
    <string name="_q143">Baby diapers decompose within 10 years.</string>
    <string name="_q144">Woodpeckers - a real threat to the development of space programs throughout the world.</string>
    <string name="_q145">In Russian felt boots is no difference between \"left\" and \"right\".</string>
    <string name="_q146">In weightlessness height increases.</string>
    <string name="_q147">Queen Victoria gave the wedding a piece of cheese.</string>
    <string name="_q148">The bulk of the extracted titanium is used to create durable alloys.</string>
    <string name="_q149">\"Balzac Age\" - from 40 years and above.</string>
    <string name="_q150">\"The game is not worth the candle,\" now means that the cost of some business higher potential income from it.</string>
    <string name="_q151">The greatest amount of hair growing on the head.</string>
    <string name="_q152">The alloy from which created the Tsar Bell contain gold and silver.</string>
    <string name="_q153">All pages created in VKontakte Today, you can see 100 years.</string>
    <string name="_q154">All pages created in VKontakte Today, you can see 100 years.</string>
    <string name="_q155">VKontakte - the most visited site in RuNet.</string>
    <string name="_q156">By accessing the site foogle.com, get on the google.com site.</string>
    <string name="_q157">Detonating cord is burning evenly.</string>
    <string name="_q158">The shortest line thinner than a human hair.</string>
    <string name="_q159">All the organs of the human body refreshed.</string>
    <string name="_q160">Earth day is 24 hours.</string>
    <string name="_q161">Earth\'s day length remains unchanged.</string>
    <string name="_q162">The highest temperature on Earth is equal to 45,5 °C.</string>
    <string name="_q163">The lowest temperature on Earth is equal to -89,1 °C.</string>
    <string name="_q164">Mercury (the planet closest to the Sun) - the hottest planet in the solar system.</string>
    <string name="_q165">Water freezes at 0 °C.</string>
    <string name="_q166">The Martian day equal to the terrestrial day.</string>
    <string name="_q167">Platinum was cheaper silver.</string>
    <string name="_q168">The magnetic field of a neutron star is a million million times larger than the Earth\'s magnetic field.</string>
    <string name="_q169">Most of iodine contained in seaweed.</string>
    <string name="_q170">Ozone protects us from solar radiation, toxic.</string>
    <string name="_q171">Some metals are not drown in the liquid.</string>
    <string name="_q172">From the consumption of ordinary table salt to die for.</string>
    <string name="_q173">Soap bubble bursts faster than the duration of a nuclear reaction.</string>
    <string name="_q174">Underground water is more than in all the oceans.</string>
    <string name="_q175">Man does not see the infrared or ultraviolet radiation.</string>
    <string name="_q176">The atomic clock always shows the correct time.</string>
    <string name="_q177">The temperature of the resulting person below the temperature of the sun.</string>
    <string name="_q178">The Martian atmosphere contains carbon dioxide.</string>
    <string name="_q179">Giraffes to brush his eyes blinking rapidly.</string>
    <string name="_q180">Mona Lisa displayed without eyebrows.</string>
    <string name="_q181">Eminem - the most sold-out hip-hop artist in the world.</string>
    <string name="_q182">Lunatics better not to wake, as this could ruin their psyche because of the abrupt awakening.</string>
    <string name="_q183">If you jump into the icy water, you can catch a cold.</string>
    <string name="_q184">After death of his nails and hair continue to grow for some time.</string>
    <string name="_q185">If you shave, then re-growing hair will be thicker and darker.</string>
    <string name="_q186">A man uses only 10% of his brain.</string>
    <string name="_q187">Warts may occur after contact with animals.</string>
    <string name="_q188">Before Coco Chanel\'s death has created a fund to which to this day are deductions from sales of famous perfume \"Chanel №5».</string>
    <string name="_q189">Einstein almost 9 years could not speak properly.</string>
    <string name="_q190">Russian tsar Peter I often worked as a discharge dentistry - tore bad teeth.</string>
    <string name="_q191">Albert Einstein received the Nobel Prize for the creation of the theory of relativity.</string>
    <string name="_q192">During the struggle for independence, when George Washington was still commander of the rebel army, he tried to poison tomatoes.</string>
    <string name="_q193">Eye color can change throughout life.</string>
    <string name="_q194">If you throw into the water fresh egg, it will sink.</string>
    <string name="_q195">The taste that you feel today is a bit different from the taste that you felt a week ago.</string>
    <string name="_q196">The most common words in the world: \"I love you\".</string>
    <string name="_q197">Every day, the Earth becomes 10 tons heavier.</string>
    <string name="_q198">Dolphins sleep with one eye open.</string>
    <string name="_q199">Aladdin was Iranian.</string>
    <string name="_q200">Do bats rectangular pupils.</string>
    <string name="_q201">Orca - a kind of shark.</string>
    <string name="_q202">\"Mother\" - the most popular word in the world.</string>
    <string name="_q203">Gorged itself chocolate to die for.</string>
    <string name="_q204">The most deadly creature - a shark.</string>
    <string name="_q205">Adult skeleton consists of 300 bones.</string>
    <string name="_q206">Hedgehog is back on the apple to eat it later.</string>
    <string name="_q207">Storks can sleep during the flight.</string>
    <string name="_q208">The cat was the king of Norway.</string>
    <string name="_q209">Teddy Bear was named in honor of Theodore Roosevelt.</string>
    <string name="_q210">Rats laugh from schekotok.</string>
    <string name="_q211">Married men over unmarried.</string>
    <string name="_q212">Penterafobiya - fear of Tiffany.</string>
    <string name="_q213">Giraffe\'s neck has 21 vertebrae.</string>
    <string name="_q214">In one country, people live in the cemetery.</string>
    <string name="_q215">The sum of all the numbers on the roulette wheel is equal to the number 666.</string>
    <string name="_q216">In Norway, always give way to the elderly.</string>
    <string name="_q217">Owls can not move their eyes.</string>
    <string name="_q218">Chewing gum is digested in the stomach for seven years.</string>
    <string name="_q219">Rabbits can only look forward.</string>
    <string name="_q220">Paparazzi - Italian photographer.</string>
    <string name="_q221">The strongest muscle in the human - leg muscle.</string>
    <string name="_q222">Do hippos pink milk.</string>
    <string name="_q223">The shelf life of honey - 10 years.</string>
    <string name="_q224">At the octopus has no heart.</string>
    <string name="_q225">Peanuts - a nut.</string>
    <string name="_q226">Fanta came up with the Germans.</string>
    <string name="_q227">Lake Michigan - the largest lake in the world.</string>
    <string name="_q228">The cow - the only mammal that can not jump.</string>
    <string name="_q229">Ostrich egg is cooked poultry quickly.</string>
    <string name="_q230">In India, no monkeys.</string>
    <string name="_q231">The German Shepherd Dog blue tongue.</string>
    <string name="_q232">Paper money is made from paper.</string>
    <string name="_q233">A sheet of paper can not be folded in half more than 5 times.</string>
    <string name="_q234">Bulimia - the refusal of eating food.</string>
    <string name="_q235">Whale Heart makes a 9 beats per minute.</string>
    <string name="_q236">The fastest flying insect - a wasp.</string>
    <string name="_q237">Elephant bears posterity 12 months.</string>
    <string name="_q238">Elephant - the largest animal.</string>
    <string name="_q239">Ant - the strongest insect.</string>
    <string name="_q240">The most intelligent bird - a parrot.</string>
    <string name="_q241">In some animals blood blue.</string>
    <string name="_q242">Do snails have no teeth.</string>
    <string name="_q243">Ostriches bury their heads in the sand.</string>
    <string name="_q244">Do mosquitoes have teeth.</string>
    <string name="_q245">Heart stops, even in healthy people.</string>
    <string name="_q246">In the mobile phone a lot of gold.</string>
    <string name="_q247">Crocodile Gena Soviet cartoon - not a crocodile.</string>
    <string name="_q248">Dragonfly lives 4 months.</string>
    <string name="_q249">Sharks never get sick.</string>
    <string name="_q250">All the planets in our solar system orbit in the same direction.</string>
    <string name="_q251">Medusa older dinosaurs.</string>
    <string name="_q252">Strawberries and strawberry - berries.</string>
    <string name="_q253">The Vatican has not yet recognized that the earth revolves around the sun.</string>
    <string name="_q254">An octopus has eight legs.</string>
    <string name="_q255">Ozone protects the earth from solar radiation, deadly poisonous.</string>
    <string name="_q256">All astronauts snore while sleeping in space.</string>
    <string name="_q257">Bird \"canary\" called in honor of the islands, where they found her.</string>
    <string name="_q258">Frankenstein - not a monster and his creator.</string>
    <string name="_q259">Sharks eat each other.</string>
    <string name="_q260">London - the rainiest city in Europe.</string>
    <string name="_q261">During the filming of the movie \"Spider-Man\" suit of the protagonist was stolen.</string>
    <string name="_q262">Centipede has forty feet.</string>
    <string name="_q263">The Statue of Liberty stands in New York.</string>
    <string name="_q264">In Australia, all are required to participate in the elections.</string>
    <string name="_q265">Chocolate is safe for animals.</string>
    <string name="_q266">The whip can not be faster than the speed of sound wave.</string>
    <string name="_q267">Bees kill more people than snakes.</string>
    <string name="_q268">Dolphins address each other by name.</string>
    <string name="_q269">In some countries, there is an inheritance tax.</string>
    <string name="_q270">Mass of blue whale language is much more than an elephant weight.</string>
    <string name="_q271">Sahara Desert - the driest place on Earth.</string>
    <string name="_q272">Napoleon was short.</string>
    <string name="_q273">Street nowhere in the world do not intersect with itself.</string>
    <string name="_q274">The chameleon changes color only for danger.</string>
    <string name="_q275">Mammals can not give birth to more than 10 cubs per birth.</string>
    <string name="_q276">All kinds of cat - loners.</string>
    <string name="_q277">The largest number - a trillion trillion.</string>
    <string name="_q278">A compass needle points to the north pole.</string>
    <string name="_q279">None of the animals can not drink sea water.</string>
    <string name="_q280">Chocolate is harmful to teeth.</string>
    <string name="_q281">Russian writer Korney Chukovsky in reality was called differently.</string>
    <string name="_q282">Speaking in a dream - an anomaly.</string>
    <string name="_q283">There is a country named after the chemical element.</string>
    <string name="_q284">Brad Pitt banned from visiting Russia.</string>
    <string name="_q285">The ancient Greeks saw the sky blue or green.</string>
    <string name="_q286">Shrimp, when sailing, the quietest of marine life.</string>
    <string name="_q287">There is a country to change their flag more than twenty times.</string>
    <string name="_q288">The world\'s oceans more than gold in the earth.</string>
    <string name="_q289">The oldest tree about 10,000 years.</string>
    <string name="_q290">The temperature of the ice is always the same - 0°C.</string>
    <string name="_q291">The only embalmed man of our time - Lenin.</string>
    <string name="_q292">The diameter of the table tennis ball was always the same.</string>
    <string name="_q293">All cats always fall down the legs.</string>
    <string name="_q294">\"Santa Barbara\" - the longest-running series.</string>
    <string name="_q295">The speed of light is constant.</string>
    <string name="_q296">Diamonds do not burn.</string>
    <string name="_q297">Scorpio is not susceptible to alcohol.</string>
    <string name="_q298">In space there is no gravity.</string>
    <string name="_q299">In ancient languages do not have words to describe the blue.</string>
    <string name="_q300">Different parts of the language are responsible for different taste sensations.</string>
    <string name="_a001">In humans, several times smaller muscle than the caterpillar. Thus, in the butterfly caterpillars muscles around 4000, whereas a person of less than 1000.</string>
    <string name="_a002">Record great distance that flew racing pigeon during his competition in 1990-1997 is 41,050 km and belongs to the Belle Brazil - blue pigeon, the owner of which is the Robert Koch (South Africa).</string>
    <string name="_a003">Rabbits develop a running speed of 56 km/h, hares are far ahead of them in speed - 72km/h.</string>
    <string name="_a004">The most expensive pigeon in the world is very thoroughbred racing pigeon, sold at auction in Belgium a wealthy Chinese buyer, which is laid out for him 200,000 dollars.</string>
    <string name="_a005">To combat the rabbits in the country has been specially imported myxomatosis virus, resulting in was destroyed by an eighth of Australian mammals and a huge number of unique plants. Surviving rabbits acquired immunity and continue to multiply.</string>
    <string name="_a006">Unripe tomatoes contain a toxic substance - solanine. It is also produced in ripe tomatoes are stored for a long time in the light. If you eat 2 kg of green tomatoes, it is possible to get poisoned. If tomatoes have opened today, they would have been banned for use in the EU as dangerous for the health.</string>
    <string name="_a007">The pink color of flamingos given to them from birth, and is derived from the edible small red crustaceans or algae, which contain the carotenoid.</string>
    <string name="_a008">Eritrotsinty have an oval shape, and retain after dehydration to flow, whereas human erythrocytes collide with each other. Camel - the only mammal that has oval red blood cells.</string>
    <string name="_a009">Blood temperature at the Antarctic fish can reach -1.7 °C.</string>
    <string name="_a010">Cheetahs owns the high speed of movement, reached by terrestrial beings. It can reach speeds of 96 km/h.</string>
    <string name="_a011">At night the cows emit between 90 and 190 liters of saliva necessary for chewing.</string>
    <string name="_a012">The heaviest lemon weighed 5 kilograms and has been grown in Israel.</string>
    <string name="_a013">Taste milk and its nutritional value is largely dependent on what the animal ate. If cow\'s milk a bitter taste, so she ate wormwood or other bitter herbs.</string>
    <string name="_a014">When choosing victim female mosquito guided by the carbon dioxide exhaled by the person on the thermal radiation, as well as the smell of lactic acid contained in sweat.</string>
    <string name="_a015">By their number of cows in second place after a man among mammals - a total of almost grazes the Earth 1.5 billion cows.. In Australia cows 40% more than people.</string>
    <string name="_a016">In the original work of Rudyard Kipling\'s \"Jungle Book\" Bagheera - a male character. Russian translators changed Bagira floor because the word \"Panther\" - feminine.</string>
    <string name="_a017">114 years ago, the first bike path appeared in Moscow. I pulled it along this avenue and the Leningrad Muscovites actively used at the turn of the century.</string>
    <string name="_a018">Before 1750 the best material for making violin strings were sheep intestine. And the first to come up with their use for this purpose, were Italians.</string>
    <string name="_a019">And each dolphin gets its name at birth. This fact is proved by scientists, writing a whistle signal, indicating the name, which responded to the same dolphin.</string>
    <string name="_a020">The world\'s oldest rose is in Germany - the 1000-year-old bush near the Cathedral of Hildesheim, which has almost reached the roof of the building.</string>
    <string name="_a021">Carrot was more ancient purple purple rather than yellow-orange. Modern orange carrots have been cultivated in the 17th century in Denmark.</string>
    <string name="_a022">Mudskipper - the special fish that can live not only in water but also on land, periodically updating the air supply in special bags for the cheeks. Moreover, they are able to \"walk\" on their fins!</string>
    <string name="_a023">Not all penguins live in Antarctica in the cold. On the Galapagos Islands, almost on the equator, inhabited by species under the name Galapagos penguins. Year-round temperature is +18..+28°C.</string>
    <string name="_a024">However, as well as dogs, elephants, roosters, snakes and other animals. Until 1939, Thailand was called Siam.</string>
    <string name="_a025">\"Koala\" on Australian Aboriginal word meaning \"no drink\". Eating eucalyptus, all the necessary moisture koala receives from its leaves and drink the water only occasionally - in periods of drought or during illness.</string>
    <string name="_a026">In Russian and English languages have no word for the name of the back of the knee.</string>
    <string name="_a027">A flint lighters not made of flint, and made of cerium, lanthanum, iron, magnesium and copper.</string>
    <string name="_a028">Andorra - the only country in the world with free postage.</string>
    <string name="_a029">Blood drink only female mosquitoes. However, before the wedding, they do not mind a drink of water or plant sap. Males eat it throughout his life.</string>
    <string name="_a030">The most expensive in the world of caviar in the world - it\'s caviar \"Almas\" yellow eggs of beluga albino. It sells for about $2,000 per 100 grams.</string>
    <string name="_a031">The shortest TV spots - video 3-second advertising the \"Guinness World Records\" in 1993, was shown on British television in 1992.</string>
    <string name="_a032">\"Travel club\" - the only Russian TV program, ranked in the Guinness Book of Records as the longest-running television project, and its leading Yuri Senkevich - as the owner of the longest career of TV presenter.</string>
    <string name="_a033">The most popular girl\'s name in the world - Anna. His nearly 100 million are women.</string>
    <string name="_a034">The prototype of the literary character of Professor FF Transfiguration in the novel \"Heart of a Dog\" is VY Danilevsky, academician, director of the Institute Organoterapevticheskogo founded in 1919.</string>
    <string name="_a035">Composer John Cage wrote music for organ called Organ2 / ASLP (As SLow as Possible). It is the product of a long human history. The organ in the German town of Halberstadt started to perform it in 2001, and is scheduled through the end of 639 years, in 2640.</string>
    <string name="_a036">Polar bears black leather. Black color helps absorb bears sunlight they need to warm.</string>
    <string name="_a037">In the Aboriginal language diirbalu four genera - male, female, middle and edible.</string>
    <string name="_a038">Pope Carlo from \"The Adventures of Pinocchio\" Alexei Tolstoy named in honor of the author of \"The Adventures of Pinocchio\" by Carlo Collodi.</string>
    <string name="_a039">The subject of the fine arts (international definition) is considered to be an object that: 1) its founder considers such, and 2) there is at least one person who agrees with him.</string>
    <string name="_a040">The United Nations - only six official languages: English, French, Arabic, Chinese, Russian and Spanish.</string>
    <string name="_a041">In Japan, a rose bred, whose day the bright red petals and white evening. Variety called \"Chameleon\".</string>
    <string name="_a042">The device consists of a platform on which the dog can stand up and make their case. When the dog leaves, then a special scraper automatically removes all under the platform, and from there into the sewer.</string>
    <string name="_a043">Starfish has 5 eyes, 5 cookies and 5 gills.</string>
    <string name="_a044">Lightning hit it from top to bottom and from bottom to top on the air suction passage by choosing the shortest distance from the ground to the cloud. Man sees that lightning strikes from the top, because of the properties of the different layers of the atmosphere.</string>
    <string name="_a045">Chinese typewriters have up to 5700 characters. The width of the keyboard on them is about one meter, and the fastest and most professional typist reaches print speeds of only 11 words per minute. Chinese computer keyboards are built on a different principle.</string>
    <string name="_a046">Sundresses in Russia originally named menswear. It was a long, swing dress with sleeves. The word \"sundress\" comes from the Persian \"Serapio\" and translated as \"honorable clothes.\"</string>
    <string name="_a047">Men\'s skirt part of the dress uniform is not just the Scottish war, but also the Greek.</string>
    <string name="_a048">Blondes in the world will not remain after 200 years. Gene, through which the light born natural blondes, gradually disappears. Blond child is born only when blonds are not only his parents, but the parents and the parents.</string>
    <string name="_a049">The great playwright has created a good remake. \"The Tragedy of Hamlet, Prince of Denmark\" (1603), was based on an ancient Scandinavian stories.</string>
    <string name="_a050">99% of living creatures that lived on Earth - are extinct.</string>
    <string name="_a051">Coin lowest esteem ever minted in Russia - polpolushki (1/8 penny).</string>
    <string name="_a052">The tribe practiced Sakayev duel peacock feathers. Sakai to be seen as the winner, should force the enemy to laugh by tickling.</string>
    <string name="_a053">\"Golden disc\" means that the disk copies sold for a million dollars, and \"Platinum Disc\" - which sold a million copies of the disc.</string>
    <string name="_a054">Sun actually white rather than yellow. Yellow tones of the sun gives the phenomenon called \"atmospheric scattering.\"</string>
    <string name="_a055">Tapeworms when lack of food can eat up to 95% of their body weight.</string>
    <string name="_a056">Tooth enamel - the most solid fabric produced by the human body.</string>
    <string name="_a057">\"Hermitage\" in French means \"place of solitude.\"</string>
    <string name="_a058">Point font or typographical manuscript weighs approximately 0.00000013 grams.</string>
    <string name="_a059">The duration of one \"year\" on this planet Pluto - 247.7 Earth years.</string>
    <string name="_a060">Coffee - it is the second largest commodity in international trade. The first place is occupied by oil.</string>
    <string name="_a061">Bassoon always made only from maple.</string>
    <string name="_a062">If one of monozygotic twins is not enough of a tooth, a missing tooth and the other twin.</string>
    <string name="_a063">Australia moving at 8.44 cm per year. Among all over the world it is the most mobile.</string>
    <string name="_a064">Fresh milk contains as much vitamin C as it found in oranges. The greatest amount of vitamin C is found in the wild rose.</string>
    <string name="_a065">A mole can dig a hole and hide in it for one minute. During the night he is able to dig a tunnel 68 meters long.</string>
    <string name="_a066">Neanderthal brain was larger than that of modern man.</string>
    <string name="_a067">Nursery rhyme \"Humpty Dumpty\" is dedicated to King Richard III, who actually fell off the wall during a battle in 1485.</string>
    <string name="_a068">40 hair grows consistently from one hair follicle during the life.</string>
    <string name="_a069">It becomes gaseous iron, heated to 5000°C.</string>
    <string name="_a070">Approximately 1/3 of the Earth\'s terrestrial surface is desert.</string>
    <string name="_a071">In Japan, there is a channel that is 24 hours a day, shows fish. Channel called \"Antistress TV.\"</string>
    <string name="_a072">The surface area of human lungs is approximately equal to the area of a tennis court.</string>
    <string name="_a073">The real name of Jean-Claude Van Damme - Varenburg.</string>
    <string name="_a074">Every year more than 50,000 earthquakes shake the Earth.</string>
    <string name="_a075">Snakes do not have ears. But their language is so sensitive to sound vibrations, they can very well distinguish any sound.</string>
    <string name="_a076">Reading a story \"Boldly Buzzing Fly\" Chukovsky, children are often asked what \"Boldly Buzzing\"? Explanatory Dictionary of the Russian Language, edited by TF Ephraim explains Tsokotukha, then. razg.-reducing. -Piet, Chatterbox.</string>
    <string name="_a077">The weight of the largest diamond ever found on Earth (before treatment) amounted to 3,106 carats.</string>
    <string name="_a078">Absolutely pure gold is very soft, it is possible to knead by hand.</string>
    <string name="_a079">Grapes explode in the microwave.</string>
    <string name="_a080">It can be drowned, but not to die. The term \"drowning\" means water from entering the lungs, and optionally associated with death.</string>
    <string name="_a081">Since 1901, 16 daredevils have gone down in the barrel over Niagara Falls. It survived only 11 people.</string>
    <string name="_a082">Mrs. Peggy Lynn gave birth to a daughter, Hannah November 11, 1995, and her brother Eric - February 2nd, 1996, 84 days later. This is the biggest difference between the appearance of twins born.</string>
    <string name="_a083">Arab numbers do not actually Arab, they were invented in India.</string>
    <string name="_a084">Every year 567 billion eggs consumed in the world.</string>
    <string name="_a085">Sheep\'s milk used to produce Roquefort cheese.</string>
    <string name="_a086">Mickey Mouse has received a star on the Walk of Fame in Hollywood.</string>
    <string name="_a087">The oldest plants - algae, existing on Earth for at least 1,000 million years.</string>
    <string name="_a088">Most of the dust in the house is a dead layer of skin.</string>
    <string name="_a089">Only 1% of the bacteria causing diseases in humans.</string>
    <string name="_a090">In the language of the Inuit names for snow there are more than 20 words.</string>
    <string name="_a091">The International Space Station has a bell. It hit every time there is a change of captain.</string>
    <string name="_a092">In Australia rabbits greater than people in China.</string>
    <string name="_a093">Cinderella, running away from the ball, lost his left shoe.</string>
    <string name="_a094">Man - the most long-lived mammal on Earth.</string>
    <string name="_a095">It appears in our galaxy each year about 40 new stars.</string>
    <string name="_a096">The Papuan language tangma only two words to describe the color, namely: muli - black, green; mola - white, red, yellow.</string>
    <string name="_a097">Each year from bee stings more people die than from snakebites.</string>
    <string name="_a098">In Russia, healers often treated plots, spells. Mumble, chatter until the beginning of the XIX century were called lies.</string>
    <string name="_a099">Pasted on the envelope rotated a postage stamp bearing the British monarch, you commit an act of high treason.</string>
    <string name="_a100">The electron is 2000 times lighter than a proton.</string>
    <string name="_a101">Buddha died at the age of 84 years.</string>
    <string name="_a102">The most \"dead\" lake is the Death on the island of Sicily. On its shores there is no vegetation, and every creature that falls into it, die, because with the bottom of the lake beat two sources of concentrated sulfuric acid.</string>
    <string name="_a103">In Pensacola, Florida law requires residents always carry at least ten dollars.</string>
    <string name="_a104">the head of an elephant brain weighs only about 0.27% by weight of his body.</string>
    <string name="_a105">In the XIX century in England was a gentleman in every whistle. A trill - a gentleman needed a cab. Two trill - two-wheeled cart. Three trilling - the police.</string>
    <string name="_a106">Santa Claus in Finnish \"Joulupukki\", in translation - Christmas goat is the case, the name is derived from the old Finnish tradition when people dressed in goat costumes and went from house to house, eating the remaining food after Christmas ...</string>
    <string name="_a107">The Russian car Zaporozhets 968M at the feet of the driver under the rug, was designed by a special hatch for winter fishing.</string>
    <string name="_a108">In Russia, the \"diamond\" - artificially rough diamond (from the French \"brilliant\" - «Brilliant\").</string>
    <string name="_a109">At the same time see the sun and the rainbow without the use of mirrors is not possible, because the center of the circle, which describes the rainbow, always lies on the line passing through the sun and the observer\'s eye.</string>
    <string name="_a110">If fuse together the entire global stock of gold, which is 32 thousand. Tonnes, the result is a cube with a side of only 12 meters.</string>
    <string name="_a111">Despite the fact that the terms \"vessel\" and \"ship\" in everyday speech are used as synonyms, in maritime terminology only military ships are swimming facilities, it should be called civil courts.</string>
    <string name="_a112">According to the Gregorian calendar days in February may be 28 or 29, depending on whether or not a leap year, but the history of known three cases where in some countries in February was 30 days, for example, in 1712 in Sweden.</string>
    <string name="_a113">According to the Gregorian calendar days in February may be 28 or 29, depending on whether or not a leap year, but the history of known three cases where in some countries in February was 30 days, for example, in 1712 in Sweden.</string>
    <string name="_a114">The largest screw-nuts weigh 4.74 m each have an external diameter of 132 cm and 63.5-cm thread.</string>
    <string name="_a115">Sirius, along with four bright stars of the constellation Canis Major is depicted on the flag of Brazil.</string>
    <string name="_a116">Initially, the logo of the company Nestle was a bird and three chicks in the nest. In 1988, during the next re-branding logo lost one chick.</string>
    <string name="_a117">One astronaut as part of the Apollo-11 crew did not set foot on the lunar surface. It\'s Michael Collins, he piloted spacecraft to orbit the Moon, while two of his colleagues have been working on the satellite.</string>
    <string name="_a118">Rubik\'s cube from any position can be assembled in 20 moves.</string>
    <string name="_a119">According to the Guinness Book of Records, Thai alphabet - the second largest in the world. The biggest alphabet in the world - Khmer.</string>
    <string name="_a120">Banknote 2 dollars there. However, it is considered unlucky, it refused to take as salary or surrender.</string>
    <string name="_a121">Darwin crater on the Moon has no relation to the researcher who created the theory of evolution. The crater is named in honor of his son (Francis Darwin), who proposed a theory of the origin of the Moon.</string>
    <string name="_a122">The top of Mount Everest is made up of blocks, which were formed on the sea floor millions of years ago.</string>
    <string name="_a123">May 6, 1999 at the factory in Finland made teddy bear rising 7.68 meters and weighing 800 kg.</string>
    <string name="_a124">These words left the language of the Emperor Vespasian, at a time when native son shamed head of the family for the introduction of a tax on the use of the toilet in public places to enrich their coffers.</string>
    <string name="_a125">All existing circuses of the world have the same diameter of the arena. It is 13 meters or 42 feet.</string>
    <string name="_a126">Bread was invented by mistake more than 7,500 years ago. The first loaf made the ancient Egyptians, who accidentally left a mixture of flour and water in a warm oven overnight. When he returned, he found a soft dough, a much more appetizing than solid cakes, which he was trying to cook.</string>
    <string name="_a127">St. Petersburg - the capital of the trams. The length of the tram tracks in the city is more than 600 km. In the 90th years of XX century this fact was recorded in the Guinness Book of Records.</string>
    <string name="_a128">Most people in Japan and China can not drink milk - after consumption of dairy products they appear symptoms of poisoning.</string>
    <string name="_a129">Asteroids 4147, 4148, 4149 and 4150 are named after \"The Beatles\": John Lennon, Paul McCartney, George Harrison and Ringo Starr, respectively.</string>
    <string name="_a130">\"Fanta\" - the world\'s third most popular soft drink after the \"Pepsi\" and \"Coca-Cola\".</string>
    <string name="_a131">\"Big Ben\" - a bell, which is located behind the clock face in the Tower of St. Stephen\'s, and not the tower itself, and not even the clock on it.</string>
    <string name="_a132">In very rare cases, a baby tooth does not fall, because no indigenous underneath. With proper care with milk tooth can live life.</string>
    <string name="_a133">The biggest snowman ice cream was constructed in Moscow. His height is about 2 meters, and weight - 300 kilograms.</string>
    <string name="_a134">If Moscow subway station escalator is not - then the depth of its occurrence less than 10 m if the escalator is only on output - up to 15 m.</string>
    <string name="_a135">The greatest height from which ever fell and is broken raw egg - 198 meters. The record set by David S. Donohue, who was on board the helicopter 2 October 1979 eggs fell to the site golf course in Tokyo, Japan.</string>
    <string name="_a136">Filipino \"Pearl of Allah\" is listed in the Guinness Book of Records (6.35 kg, 32 000 carats, diameter 238 millimeters).</string>
    <string name="_a137">Fingers are never perfectly straight. As a rule, index, ring finger and little finger is slightly curved toward the middle finger, while the middle finger can be bent in different directions.</string>
    <string name="_a138">The vowel sound \"A\" - the most common in the world\'s languages. No language in which it would not be such a sound. He is even in Abkhazia, where only two vowels - \"A\" and \"E\", and Ubykh, where \"A\" - the only vowel.</string>
    <string name="_a139">London post offices still accept letters addressed to no one Sherlock Holmes, residing at Baker Street 221B.</string>
    <string name="_a140">The most common diseases in the world are various periodontal disease, such as gingivitis (gum inflammation). Few people on the planet manage to avoid one or another of its forms.</string>
    <string name="_a141">Almost every chewing gum manufacturers add dyes. Are often found on the packaging of E171 was previously banned in Russia. This dye is called titanium white. Now their use in foods is acceptable, but be aware that the dye can cause liver and kidney disease.</string>
    <string name="_a142">Sandals age 9500 years have been found in a cave in central Oregon. They were made from the bark of the tree wormwood.</string>
    <string name="_a143">Baby diapers decompose for 250 years and occupy 1% of all musorok.</string>
    <string name="_a144">Woodpeckers are a great danger to the fuel tanks of spacecraft, they can harm the skin of the ship. At the launch site staff constantly monitors that the birds do not appear on the site. They were deterred by special balloons.</string>
    <string name="_a145">Each of them is formed by the toe, taking the form of a host of foot. valenki dimensions in centimeters, so it is very easy to find the right size, foot length measurements and adding 2 cm. \"shrinkage\".</string>
    <string name="_a146">All the people in weightlessness than about five centimeters. On Earth, gravity pressure on the spine, but in space on the spine does not press anything, and he crushes the entire length.</string>
    <string name="_a147">One of Queen Victoria\'s wedding gifts was a piece of cheese, weighing half a ton and a diameter of three meters.</string>
    <string name="_a148">Only 7% of the titanium produced in the world is used in mechanical engineering. 13% goes to the production of paper, 20% - in the production of plastic, and 60% - in the production of paint.</string>
    <string name="_a149">The expression \"Balzac Age\" emerged after the novel by French writer Honore de Balzac \"Thirty Woman\" in 1831, and is relevant only in relation to women 30 to 40 years.</string>
    <string name="_a150">The expression \"game is not worth the candle\" arose from a speech of card players. They talked about so modest gain, does not pay the cost of the burnt-out candles during the game.</string>
    <string name="_a151">Only 2% of the hairs that grow on the human body, fall on his head.</string>
    <string name="_a152">The chemical composition of the alloy material of the Tsar Bell is as follows: copper - 84.51%, tin - 13.21%, sulfur - 1,25%, gold - 0.036%, silver - 0.25%.</string>
    <string name="_a153">To view all the pages of people who are registered VKontakte, will take about 1000 years.</string>
    <string name="_a154">To view all the pages of people who are registered VKontakte, will take about 1000 years.</string>
    <string name="_a155">VKontakte is the third largest in RuNet, second only to Yandex and Mail.ru. Every day, the site comes nearly a million people.</string>
    <string name="_a156">Google Company (owner of the domain foofle.com) forwards all sealed on google.com.</string>
    <string name="_a157">Fuse burns at a constant rate of 1 cm/s. He estimated the length of the sappers time before the explosion.</string>
    <string name="_a158">Most small division of the smallest line thickness is equal to 18 atoms. The thickness of a human hair is equal to the total length of 5 lines.</string>
    <string name="_a159">The man is updated everything but the teeth. On the other hand, an alligator, falls and rises again around 3000 teeth throughout life.</string>
    <string name="_a160">Earth day is 23 hours 56 minutes 4 seconds. introduced an extra day every four years (leap year, on February 29) to correct this inequality.</string>
    <string name="_a161">After 250 million. Years day will last 25.5 hours due to the slowing of Earth\'s rotation around its axis.</string>
    <string name="_a162">The highest temperature was recorded in El Azizia (Libya) and amounted to 56.7 ° C.</string>
    <string name="_a163">The lowest temperature was recorded on Soviet Antarctic station \"Vostok\" (Vostochnoya Antarctica) and amounted to -89,2 ° C.</string>
    <string name="_a164">The hottest planet in the solar system - Venus. Unlike Mercury, it is the atmosphere, which accumulates heat.</string>
    <string name="_a165">Very pure water in a vessel with smooth walls can cool to -38 ° C - such water is called \"supercooled\". At this time, it is very unstable, and any shock or the appearance of bubbles will lead to instantaneous transformation into ice.</string>
    <string name="_a166">The Martian day is 24 hours 39 minutes 35.244 seconds, which is very close to the earth.</string>
    <string name="_a167">Platinum in Spanish literally means \"silver\". Such a dismissive name platinum was given conquistadors. The fact is that being very refractory, platinum did not give melting and valued twice lower than silver.</string>
    <string name="_a168">Neutron stars are the strongest magnets in the Universe.</string>
    <string name="_a169">Most of the iodine contained in peas (211 micrograms per 1 kg. Of dry weight), followed by peppers (135), a bow (19), salad (17).</string>
    <string name="_a170">Ozone is highly toxic, it is more toxic than carbon monoxide.</string>
    <string name="_a171">Lithium - a very light metal. It emerges, for example, kerosene.</string>
    <string name="_a172">For a person weighing 80 kg is a lethal dose of a quarter pound packs.</string>
    <string name="_a173">Bubble bursts for 0.001 second. Nuclear reaction proceeds 0.000 000 000 000 000 001 seconds.</string>
    <string name="_a174">As part of the mantle of Earth\'s water is contained in 10-12 times more than in the oceans.</string>
    <string name="_a175">1% of people can see infrared and 1% - ultraviolet radiation.</string>
    <string name="_a176">Atomic clocks have an error of 1 second in six million years.</string>
    <string name="_a177">The highest temperature created by man, - 510 million °C, which is 30 times higher than the temperature in the center of the sun.</string>
    <string name="_a178">The atmosphere of Mars is 95% carbon dioxide.</string>
    <string name="_a179">Giraffes clean the eyes of their 45-centimeter tongue.</string>
    <string name="_a180">Mona Lisa in the picture no eyebrows.</string>
    <string name="_a181">Eminem is in the \"Guinness Book of Records\" as the most sold-out hip-hop artist in the world.</string>
    <string name="_a182">In fact, it is a delusion, much more damage can cause injury from a collision with a door jamb, if the person does not wake up. But to do it is soft, then help him to return to bed.</string>
    <string name="_a183">There is no evidence to support this. Yes, the most common viruses in the winter period of low humidity, but more likely to get much higher than indoors, where a lot of people. The only thing that can make the cold - to reduce the resistance of the body of the infection, which is already in the body.</string>
    <string name="_a184">This is misleading, in fact after the death of the human skin is dehydrated and compressed, because it seems that hair and nails are longer.</string>
    <string name="_a185">Unshaven hair narrowed over time, and therefore appear to be more subtle than regrowing. In addition, over time the hair becomes lighter because of the sun, which also creates the impression that the new hair darker.</string>
    <string name="_a186">This idea was picked up, misinterpreted as if the remaining 90% of the brain is not used at all. In these 10% are utilized alternately from different parts of the brain, and without the other 90% of their work is impossible.</string>
    <string name="_a187">Human warts caused by a virus, which only affects people - papilloma (pappiloma). They can not be passed from animals with warts, and even more so from the toads.</string>
    <string name="_a188">The funds under the will of the great patron spent to support young artists and writers.</string>
    <string name="_a189">His parents believed he would be retarded.</string>
    <string name="_a190">It is sometimes carried away, and under the hand could get practically healthy.</string>
    <string name="_a191">In fact, the Nobel Committee awarded him the prize for the discovery of the photoelectric effect of the laws.</string>
    <string name="_a192">Tomato at the time was considered poisonous.</string>
    <string name="_a193">Sometimes shortly after birth eye color varies from light to dark, and is associated with the accumulation of melanin in the iris. Also eye color can be changed, and in connection with certain diseases.</string>
    <string name="_a194">If you throw into the water fresh egg, it will sink, and stale - pops up. This is due to the generation of gas inside the eggs during storage.</string>
    <string name="_a195">Taste buds on the human tongue live an average of 7-10 days, and then die and are replaced by new ones.</string>
    <string name="_a196">The most common three words: \"Made in China\".</string>
    <string name="_a197">Due meteorites and cosmic dust earth heavier daily for at least 10 tons.</string>
    <string name="_a198">Dolphins sleep each hemisphere of the brain at a time. Closes his eyes only sleeping hemisphere.</string>
    <string name="_a199">Ancient book \"A Thousand Tales\" reads: Aladdin was a little Chinese boy.</string>
    <string name="_a200">Rectangular pupils only have goats, sheep, octopus.</string>
    <string name="_a201">Orca - a kind of dolphin.</string>
    <string name="_a202">The most popular word \"OK\".</string>
    <string name="_a203">After eating 10 kg of chocolate, a person can die.</string>
    <string name="_a204">The female mosquito - the most deadly creature on the planet.</string>
    <string name="_a205">Skeleton 300 includes bone only at birth to 25 years and 206 only in the skeleton bone remains healthy person.</string>
    <string name="_a206">Juice secreted apple hedgehog helps to get rid of parasites.</string>
    <string name="_a207">Storks can sleep on the fly.</string>
    <string name="_a208">King of Norway was a dog.</string>
    <string name="_a209">Teddy Bear was named in honor of Theodore Roosevelt.</string>
    <string name="_a210">If you tickle a rat, she would laugh.</string>
    <string name="_a211">The average unmarried man married below.</string>
    <string name="_a212">Penterafobiya - a psychological disorder from the hostility of communication with the mother of his wife.</string>
    <string name="_a213">In the giraffe only 7 vertebrae, just like any other mammal.</string>
    <string name="_a214">In Thailand, the relatives of the deceased sometimes live in the family crypt.</string>
    <string name="_a215">Indeed, the sum of all the numbers on a roulette wheel is the number 666.</string>
    <string name="_a216">Norway is not accepted to give way to the elderly because in their opinion, the most points to their physical limitations.</string>
    <string name="_a217">Owls can not move their eyes, but they can be rotated 270 degrees on the neck.</string>
    <string name="_a218">Chewing gum is not digested at all, but comes out of the body naturally.</string>
    <string name="_a219">Rabbits can see what they have going on behind his back.</string>
    <string name="_a220">The Italian paparazzi - annoying mosquito.</string>
    <string name="_a221">Language - the most powerful muscle in humans.</string>
    <string name="_a222">Yes, a pink hippo milk.</string>
    <string name="_a223">Honey - the only natural product that never goes bad.</string>
    <string name="_a224">At octopus three hearts.</string>
    <string name="_a225">Peanut relates to the legume family.</string>
    <string name="_a226">The new drink invented the German subsidiary of Coca-Cola when he could not get a concentrate of Coca-Cola because of the war.</string>
    <string name="_a227">The largest lake in the world - Russia\'s Lake Baikal.</string>
    <string name="_a228">The only animal that can not jump - the elephant.</string>
    <string name="_a229">Ostrich egg is cooked for about four hours.</string>
    <string name="_a230">In India, more than 50 million monkeys.</string>
    <string name="_a231">Blue tongue only breed of dog chow-chow.</string>
    <string name="_a232">Banknotes made from cotton.</string>
    <string name="_a233">A sheet of paper can not be folded in half more than 7 times.</string>
    <string name="_a234">Bulimia - an indomitable appetite.</string>
    <string name="_a235">Indeed, the heart of the whale makes a 9 beats per minute.</string>
    <string name="_a236">Dragonflies fly faster than anyone. They reach speeds up to 100 km / h.</string>
    <string name="_a237">Elephant bears posterity 22 months.</string>
    <string name="_a238">The largest animal - the blue whale.</string>
    <string name="_a239">The strongest insect - Beetle rhinoceros. He is able to lift the weight is 850 times heavier than its own weight.</string>
    <string name="_a240">The most intelligent bird - raven.</string>
    <string name="_a241">Blue blood in octopuses.</string>
    <string name="_a242">Do snails 25,000 teeth.</string>
    <string name="_a243">Ostriches do not bury their heads in the sand. It is a myth.</string>
    <string name="_a244">Do mosquitoes 22 tooth.</string>
    <string name="_a245">During sneezing heart stops for a moment.</string>
    <string name="_a246">In the mobile phone more gold than 17 tons of gold ore.</string>
    <string name="_a247">In crocodiles, when the mouth is closed, the teeth stick out. Alligators - no. Crocodile Gena in Russian cartoon - alligator.</string>
    <string name="_a248">Life expectancy of a dragonfly - not more than 24 hours.</string>
    <string name="_a249">Sharks immunity to all known human diseases.</string>
    <string name="_a250">Venus and Uranus rotate in the opposite direction.</string>
    <string name="_a251">Jellyfish exist in the world, more than 650 million years. This means that they have hundreds of millions of years older than the dinosaurs.</string>
    <string name="_a252">Tasty red pulp, which is all so like to eat, actually is overgrown receptacle, and small seeds, nuts on the surface and eat the fruit. Strawberries and strawberry - nut.</string>
    <string name="_a253">Only in 1992 the Vatican officially acknowledged that the earth revolves around the sun.</string>
    <string name="_a254">Do not octopus eight legs and two. The remaining six tentacles are hands. So correct octopus called \"six-armed biped.\"</string>
    <string name="_a255">For a man ozone dangerous carbon monoxide. Fortunately, unlike the odorless carbon monoxide, ozone is easy to detect - it smells like geraniums.</string>
    <string name="_a256">Orbiting astronauts never snore - snoring in weightlessness is not possible.</string>
    <string name="_a257">The name \"canary\" came from the Canary Islands. However, \"lslas Canarias\" in Spanish does not mean the birds, and the Isle of Dogs.</string>
    <string name="_a258">The protagonist of the novel by Mary Shelley\'s \"Frankenstein\" - Dr. Frankenstein. He\'s not a monster, and the monster\'s creator, has no name.</string>
    <string name="_a259">Embryos tiger sharks are fighting each other in the womb. Born only one who ate all the rest.</string>
    <string name="_a260">London drops 590 millimeters, whereas in Rome a year - 760, and in Milan - about 1000 mm. It turns out \"wet\" London - in fact, one of the driest cities in Europe.</string>
    <string name="_a261">On the film \"Spider-Man\" costume was stolen 4 protagonist worth 50 thousand dollars each.</string>
    <string name="_a262">All centipedes an odd number of pairs of legs, and none is not exactly forty feet.</string>
    <string name="_a263">The Statue of Liberty is not in New York. Cvobody Island (Liberty Island), nA which it is installed, geographically belongs to the state of New Jersey.</string>
    <string name="_a264">In Australia, the absence of citizens to the polls without a valid reason shall be punished with a large fine.</string>
    <string name="_a265">Chocolate is very toxic to animals. A small bird kill at least 10 grams of chocolate a dog - not more than two hundred. Unlike humans, animals can not split the chocolate contained in the alkaloid theobromine.</string>
    <string name="_a266">The tip of the whip with the impact of a speed exceeding the speed of sound. Click whip occurs when breaking the sound barrier to them.</string>
    <string name="_a267">Bees are much deadlier than the snake. As a result of allergic reactions from bee stings each year are killed far more people than from snake bites.</string>
    <string name="_a268">Dolphin communication system is so developed, that each dolphin has its own name, to which he responds when he is addressed relatives.</string>
    <string name="_a269">One of the most hated tax in the United Kingdom and the United States - is the inheritance tax, which can reach 55%.</string>
    <string name="_a270">The weight of a blue whale language only occasionally can be up to 4 tons. This corresponds to the average weight of an African elephant.</string>
    <string name="_a271">The driest place on Earth - not the Sahara, and the area in Antarctica called the Dry Valleys. These valleys are free from ice and snow and have not seen rain for over two million years.</string>
    <string name="_a272">With the growth of 5 feet 7 inches (170 cm) - slightly higher than the average inhabitant of the French 18th century.</string>
    <string name="_a273">The only street in the world, which forms an intersection with itself - The planning is a street in Novosibirsk (Russia).</string>
    <string name="_a274">The chameleon changes color, not only in order to disguise, but also depending on the mood, reflecting, for example, hunger, fear or threat.</string>
    <string name="_a275">Female bristly hedgehog, or streaked inhabiting Madagascar has the most numerous brood among mammals. In one litter she brings to 25 pups.</string>
    <string name="_a276">Lions - the only cat that live in packs (prides).</string>
    <string name="_a277">The largest number used in mathematical calculations, - the number of Graham. This number is so large that all the atoms in the universe would not be enough for the ink to write it.</string>
    <string name="_a278">Compass does not point to the North Pole, and the magnetic pole of the Earth. The distance between them is more than 500 km.</string>
    <string name="_a279">Penguins can drink sea water. Excess salt is concentrated in the special salt glands and excreted through the nostrils.</string>
    <string name="_a280">Chocolate is not harmful to teeth. Moreover, it slows down the development of caries. But this does not apply to milk and chocolate to black.</string>
    <string name="_a281">In fact, his name - Nikolai Korneichuk.</string>
    <string name="_a282">Talking in his sleep from a medical point of view, are the norm. It is known that the ability to speak in his sleep is associated with dreaming, and handed down. Interestingly, the dumb speak, too, in a dream, but in sign language.</string>
    <string name="_a283">Argentina - the only country named after the chemical element. \"Argentum\" - Latin for \"silver\".</string>
    <string name="_a284">In 1997, Brad Pitt was banned from entering China because of his role in the film \"7 years in Tibet.\" The ban is still in effect.</string>
    <string name="_a285">The ancient Greeks never called green or sky blue - for them it was bronze.</string>
    <string name="_a286">Shrimp - the most noisy creature in the ocean. The noise of the big flocks of shrimp capable of \"blind\" Sonar marine vessel.</string>
    <string name="_a287">Afghanistan over the past 125 years changed the national flag and twenty-three times.</string>
    <string name="_a288">In the waters of the oceans contains a hundred times more gold than was produced in the history of mankind.</string>
    <string name="_a289">In 2008, Canadian spruce was found that sprouted from seed in the time of the Ice Age, and still give the new shoots.</string>
    <string name="_a290">Ice cold differently. The temperature of the ice of the Antarctic glaciers reach -60 ° C, the ice of Greenland glaciers - an average of -28 ° C, on the tops of the Alps - about 0°C.</string>
    <string name="_a291">Besides Lenin, the body has a lot of people embalmed and exhibited now on public display in its own mausoleum. Among nix - Mao Zedong, Kim Il Sung, Ho Chi Minh and Civil War hero Grigory Kotovsky.</string>
    <string name="_a292">By decision of the Table Tennis Federation, the ball diameter was increased by 2 mm in order to make it easier to watch the game on television.</string>
    <string name="_a293">Cats breed regdoll (Engl. \"Rag doll\") due to poor muscle tone do not have time to turn over in the air on their feet and fall on his back.</string>
    <string name="_a294">The longest series \"Guiding Light\" (eng. Guiding Light), which was shown for 57 years and consisted of 15762 series.</string>
    <string name="_a295">The speed of light is not constant and depends on the environment in which it extends. In the vacuum speed of light equal to 300,000 km / sec, the diamond - about 124,000 km / sec, and cooled to -269°C sodium - less than 60 km/h.</string>
    <string name="_a296">Diamonds are burning. Burn diamond lighter than its gold or platinum rim. At temperatures above 900°C diamonds burn without leaving any trace.</string>
    <string name="_a297">If you drop a scorpion on alcohol, he instantly go mad and sting itself to death.</string>
    <string name="_a298">The space is quite strong gravity. It makes gravity satellites revolve around the Earth, the Earth around the Sun and all the stars around the galactic center.</string>
    <string name="_a299">Neither Greek nor Chinese nor Japanese, nor even the Hebrew does not have a description of the blue.</string>
    <string name="_a300">Each area of language can experience all the sensations. The idea of a language map generally arisen because of mistranslation Harvard professor of German research.</string>
</resources>
